Thank you thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you thank
you.
Thank you thank you. Thank you
thank you.
Thank you. Thank you thank
you. For you are wired
for that sometime by the. Way
the shock of fishy about the.
American law cover up for seven years ago
when our suddenly appeared from nowhere
to claim. A little tough
on the whole B.S.P.
To life. By Marilyn Corby Thank you. Thank
you thank
you. Very much no.
Thank you.
I've been very busy field house since Mr
Colby Dallas. Was only because of your
late arrival but Mrs Low told me
to bring you here thank you always
a pleasure so. I don't mind admitting
to you frankly so but I don't feel told
myself it is that I speak of no no such.
Thing as opinion but graveyard which also
deeply all me. Yes. It is
sadder someone clinging to old
house like most on tombstone
quite like by proxy
backers for you it will.
Be the back door. At the
rear. Most interesting said we're
going to buy from going here.
This waste of. Family will
be waiting for you in here.
Comes To spoke. No not now.
Jan. I'm so glad you were right
Johnny I knew I could depend on you you
know everyone here even after the greeting
the end of my group pressuring Ray.
You're supposed to first get your
report you get carried what about.
What.
They did you believe they are you still
are not going to be certain but if so
suspect life may be in danger
nor do you see them. Or the one
that. Likes. To create an impression
this fellow may be impossible to
complete. These days by French
and British consul indicate he
is really ALAN KOHLER Because the way he
went all these years before communicating
with his family investigation prove ALAN
KOHLER be listed in French Foreign Legion
was taken prisoner by Reeves escaped only
recently could not have communicated
sooner then as he was crowned we can expect
him to appear at any time to claim the
estate he has
a right to the money well then we
have. For you to come Rick. First
of all women come up. To see
you and then we'll be there in
a moment and see that we're not disturbed.
I can't stand net men staring at me while
we get rid of it we've gone over that
part you're. Probably going to be emphatic
Mr Chairman by the way you may not be
interested in the same I am sure you will
be. Tonight measurable and has promised
us
a message concerning our I would like to
have you press would appreciate very much
. Chinese people interested
in all things like.
Having started to fail and she had already
just about to begin with facts you're
always causing me grief if we'd been
right but it would have been curious.
Get. Your Mr Archer
knowledge in May Good
to meet you I've heard
a lot about you I'm Dick Williams of the
globe anything I could put on the cool be
patient and I think a publication
big eyes you repeatedly to consider
a family affair is confidential. Just
to gauge whether why the best place for
a skeleton is in the family closet
thank you nothing to say. I'm sorry.
This is professional Our advice Thank you
Christian and issues our media karma
so please. Most fortunate get to be able
to cross the bridge to do well in place of
honor believe and sisters. Shall we
begin if you will take you you see we
come and.
Take this chair County we might be
all right I don't write. Tonight.
I wish to us for your special concentration.
We will try to bring word of Colby
from the beyond. Maybe difficult. We
should ask use far in our code be
wary of being our guy
before push. We will pause
a moment you may be. Sticky
when you turn the lights.
The person here.
For now I. AM
If they are written here.
He wants to come to you.
Colby.
Notify police immediately.
Thank. You you know what beats me is how
I don't call be got to shore without
arguing with somebody new and that's how
we try to go to be here and finish him off
yes he must be trapped all right you know
I was the five of the five of them so
night. If it's time for all I get would not
fit the coffee or sorry the fingerprint
. Gloves or I get this fellow
smart enough for that.
Phone the resting place of their weapon
I've already checked their fingerprints
What do you find are right.
For our eyes you want an
autopsy on there's
a very few more. Than any
other room yes I was.
You to Williams I want to talk to everyone
who was present here tonight. You must
have been pretty sure Colby was there when
you started your saying that isn't true
we were merely seeking
a measure concerning him just before
this terrible thing happened I felt
a strange new person. I knew we were
in contact Allen called the Spirit.
And with his body hidden behind the panel
it was easy for his spirit to get here
wasn't it grew up simply.
Because of covert
separation from family and the child
that been a quarrel or rather
a misunderstanding between Alan and his
father your seat and you share the
thank you. Very thing the family affair
that we're looking for facts is all I
wanted was
a motive I wouldn't have to go any further
than the law family what do you mean by
simple enough isn't it I want
Colby alive meant the loss of
a fortune for all of you who saw her
again through. Money from Kobe's
face used for psychic research as executor
of these things. Only start somewhere
where you saw fit to donate.
To Colby in return.
Yes I suppose so. Were
you here earlier today.
For your. Stuff I overexpose about six
o'clock to remind him to have everything in
order for the seance you were
here but how do you know I've had
a slight cold and I have told most
immediately to take it up is. That
right.
Cutie off to. You were here all day good.
Danger did not know and then
Koby had to write oh shit one.
This side Professor Bush
visited today. Why I was here.
You are so hot for he came here to meet
me and I thought the power of the fray at
the time was that I was
here first I was given
a five thirty I'm sure of the time because
I noticed the clock was fast and I was
about to recite.
Three. Ancient clocks that
it made this time not.
Fixed. Well.
Reset the clock you don't think I'm
lying to you you. Are quite time
barred quarter and the murder took place
around five o'clock I can tell you more
than there was nothing wrong when I was
if. You were planning to get married
shortly weren't you why yes. One off.
Gradually should we have enough of it can
we be sure my fears but until is
rather a so be all the time to give me
a part of this I know they need
that's all. You can do scream.
For the police department. If you
any ideas which. Saw through your.
OK We've got
a box of eyes for. You in the morning
thank you we're bringing extras. I
mean I'm very they don't write.
For more finished. Plate. Thank
you so I think we're pretty.
Specially when they go there should you.
As with I call fingerprints signature
clearly if you leave the room it's just
like confession. Fingerprints event
event or. Detective can catch the owner
of figures right. Then I think in
this thing. That somebody would see
a. Car. Excuse. OK
Come along with us we put you up. Thank you
so much but with your permission maybe
spend the night here here this would like
to make more complete investigation.
As you wish I should prepare one of the
papers and you had better remain here with
Mr Chen tonight. Paul
my man said gently. I
change something all of your breakfast in
the morning chatting about your breakfast
nobody knows how you like your toast but
me I know how I like my copes when I jolly
.
Fire place. Yes.
Yes yes I like that gravy. This way so.
Thank you.
For the. Political observer.
Pretty interesting stuff
very very interesting. Quite what you
said corroboration of deductions
then we can believe you had bought so should
I pack your bags thank you so much but
most of this request even assistance
in so many levels of the nation tops.
For you means that we
investigate downstairs.
Do you think they could be spirit. Very
practical spirit to enter by the door.
I can all see different gates.
Here I am. Why you can. Change
or stay here to investigate
I don't know what's going on. There's no
you return I don't tell them everything I
do think advisable facts could take you
home immediately Quite right now I think.
You'll think you'll think. I'm.
Going to be stuck in here.
Forever. Woman's intuition
like. Life to truth.
Etc back to the.
Restaurant. Put To me anything
you want to the norm and the
music always become a feel thing I
knew you were the band. I was marrying
a man of your station from the world
beyond. Sixty years. Recently.
They haven't been touched for
years. They step on paper be.
Tarnished with the. Schooling. Very young.
Boy Scout and I like. Many used.
To speak. Very simple
solution of music from.
Can't believe Professor Byrne.
Purposely to see this as the
mother of invention. Sometimes
stepmother of deception.
Distinguished Professor. Tonight.
Which. In our regular
receiving set up their.
Combinations. And characters
have been done. When I
look on reliable she cannot keep.
Her mission to try
experiments very. Light.
Then we shall be able
to do as research and.
They're all thank you so much. You
used to turn on the light is insane.
Appearance. Or be secret. Most convenient.
Maybe to. The. Peace of.
The position occupied by the deceased
but. Could I be excuse me so I are
not very good at that sort of thing
going to. Require. But really so
are. Car. Requests. For
paying the full face. Position.
On the. Evening you
say she. Really sorry.
About. Chemical Analysis
of say you. Who use of.
Me to. Find My. Own grease.
When exposed about. You. Like you never.
Could do. So. But.
Please do not moving.
But I looked really led. To back
a myriad. Invisible
ultraviolet rays to prove.
This theory of
a spook like it's always more than that
it proves that your new challenge.
He may even have. Finding my boobs by
then does not prove weeks by the way
I gave for knowing the funds he asked.
Even made provision for him comma after my
guess they knew that if Allen returned
they would never receive another penny in
for your present evidence may be wise
to change in the future I'll see to
that to help turn accounting in the state
prepared and approved. And at the same
time I am make our new will
most take precautions.
Well all right except for the punch in the
river you gave me I'm not familiar to
most every. Month and reduce my desire for
that shopping bag there's no argument
about. His Baxter. Baxter.
And you would be. Fun to do next week
just leaving here and he did such
a pretty good idea so. We got
we're not going to do you not
straight. When you think.
You. Might have somebody
tried to appear Charlie why.
I figure I could very foolishly come to get
this haven't I. Mrs Lloyd safety reason
for
a visit exactly Janice and I went to have
bedroom to say good night when I found she
wasn't there had a hunch she
was over here with you I saw
a car outside and came in
thank you so did you go home.
With facts. And something very
important like you are able to.
Course there's anything I can do now look
here Charley I want to morrow. You go
home. Oh very well come on. Thank you.
Observe and when leaving the house when
entering ground how does so begin with you
know the gate from. Three.
Someone very familiar with
the ancient house. From the.
I know this place inside and out it's
a regular honeycomb of passages that start
every where and no. You want me to show
you know. We'll investigate
honeycomb later maybe find be.
Sure to go.
At present much concerned about Mrs
know what you mean. Not so certain
gunfire directed at the top of so you think
the temp was made on her life. Maybe.
Suggest you go to police and one request
God told Mrs lower they might go
immediately.
Caretakers Varian made our. Rick's
a queer over. All good
night friend to Pam and
a very odd reason why. Alan was
you gave go. After you left home
you broke but then she committed suicide I
recall down response. Three I was having
more than one skeleton in closet.
Nothing. May question please.
You were here yesterday at
coffee. About five o'clock.
Then if Alan Corby.
Would say. I didn't hear you
doing someone should climb
over without trying if someone were
sneaking in the years to come if. You
think they'd ring the bell me no correction
please that it would not climb over
the gate would look for
a secret place. Thank you so much. Q
. O'clock.
O'clock.
Q. Q.
Q
Q Q
.
Do you. Really.
Have the informed reason for not hearing
yesterday when Alan cobia right I tell you
I didn't know you. I don't
know what I was doing.
Radio friends made. You last night
to grow our music for sale.
You're buying up there OK.
Nothing about radio. To my.
Dad. When they think
telling ten kids is cool.
Quinine please.
Read. The book. Why don't you go and ask.
Very good idea. Thank you so much.
Already
a professor from up at home hope to get
valuable information about Seances last
night can I help you thank you for.
Small point of information. I'm
in contact with spirit to find
ultraviolet light use for.
I don't understand very peculiar
circumstance and I'm Corby's face treated
with the solution the point. When exposed
to the by the light produced gold
not from spin. If what you say is true Mr
chance it has nothing to do with it. It
has never been found connected with my power
which was given me to communicate with
the other where it is never the issue.
Upmost respect through believe in psychics.
But can explain please source of
music to companies they are not yet
I'll show you.
The percent from this transmitting that
we always use music in the background for
our work. Most interesting.
Repeating device. Control
switch it could be
a house so music can be
picked up but then you Tony.
So we call it.
And we can price but you know for
us to make a go we went through
a few new of our own coffee national. You
can watch that close on us the police
won't be far behind Come on I'm not going
to I was now part of you can't prove it
to the police.
Or for you to go in there and
run. But I'm. Going to chair.
I all right. Fire crackers cop explored
in the head would be quite all right
you need the aspirin this
time Charlie. Rose for he
left just before you came in and that's
why your son isn't here you were covering
up for him to make
a getaway You're under arrest. Let's go.
Down the hall as I was an overall guest.
I want to be the first to congratulate your
child when you let the murderer of Alan
Colby slip right through your
fingers. Like who play with matches.
Even. When we pick up you
an invitation to the
ball. Thank you so much.
It is warm and dry
it must have been born to kill Colby I'm
trying to get Mrs Laura. Do you hate as
many as folks which mean you have something
on your mind what is minded president
like Hangover misspend even. Might
keep important engagement with Mrs
Gore please.
This summer one hundred hours to go before
leaving the psychic research subs from
Beijing to be administered by
a worm do you fell in behalf of my dearly
beloved friends I'll prove them Carlotta
but one. That is because you want to strike
from the will you know me well when I
wrote a new document I'll have
a grove your signature might. Have you any
idea how much these people have cost me
so far I have to check over your accounts
to get the exact amount they guy over our
the accounts tonight Mr Phelps brings
a new way of. All right what do you
bet I'm trying to create that will be
everything and be ready for me to. Stay
here to be spied on by policeman I don't
know if I recall being. Forward to my
going every And he got what was coming.
We can no harm and I'll pay you right.
In my opinion it would be better to watch
all right than the football when he
painted Allen never to kill him no one
being overlooked when weaving that could
come. Back with him you will have to make
a great thing I have those figures ready
for you by then and don't but Mr Morton
will have police got here
about his captive about. The
idea.
Very chary part of our
plans. But he didn't
say here's a. Good dinner
because you do like
a picture changer Elaine I spend
an hour here at the week of Allah.
I must repeat madam but the
face sort of thing leaves me
a little creepy. A
twenty five March just of anything happening
even one of forms couldn't get through
this place now I know in danger of like
somebody like me right quick least expected
I want to look around.
Alright my sister gave
one of the family right. Now we're getting
a chance of getting out of. Excuse
me madam.
I miss the Phelps arrived yet.
When I was.
In my view this is Lower shop to hear from
outside the house why must you question
no one and except police and prison if you
can't stop me better stay here if you
would like to see it.
Not yet but this gentleman just drove up
because I don't believe some believe him
but whatever it was our guest has I don't
see how it was done the place surrounded
by police into strange voters
should occur at exactly the point.
Well I'm speaking from a lower house not
a homicide squad in the
car. You want to hold
a bottle after the inquest of course
what happened. When the mother.
Can do nothing why did you let it
happen you knew she was in danger.
That it takes to be away from my house
when I remember what to do here along.
With. I can't go with you but I was right
I'm holding you responsible you prove the
bone was guilty of the murder of I'm going
to be you know you made an attempt on
his lows right last night yet you failed
to turn him over the police force.
Because life there or.
That kid. I'm sorry I lost my head.
I know you did the best you could.
Extend deepest sympathy. But the
loved one seemed to be taken away
remained our Was the.
Mr Baxter. To get that.
But need your help. What do you make of
this. Someone's been talking to well the
villain must have stood right here when
he fired back fatal shots no hasty
deduction like Agent take
the good from outside shot
come from high powered rifle
fired from these complete.
They are great to climb
trees. All must die so. And
for proportions limits
athletic ability. Yes.
When you give me
a leg up so. What I would. Be quiet
and you are. There is not very
much to be seen for last years to observe
a small branch right and. We are sure
brick is being cut by dipping down
with the sole thank you so much please
horn finger on branch.
From the line of vision.
Oh. My your job
earliest. Hope to establish
important facts about me and. My
exact promise of silence I promise as
somebody would say OK don't let us go.
Well what was Mr Chance. At last find use
a simple geometry. High
power would take shelter
a distance between three point.
Criminally very clever
a RAID device so high and. Dry better
to operate to go on right.
After the first shot was
fired it kept pulling the trigger did
because you grew out of the trunk Well you
know magazine was. I thought it might be
quite right but that's dangerous why when
the clock strikes again do
not disturb. The minutes I
suggest we return to your
well I was immediately.
She was sitting right there when the shot
came through the window. I don't need to
actually come right in got into any new
trouble so sorry to disappoint May I offer
a slight demonstration
please help yourself.
Once you are going to be into
your decorating. Want to try
a couple of sunflowers in truces live
on Chinese are quite sufficient.
I don't know if you've time
to wait just got back.
Are you all right back
to. You when Charlie
what's the answer. To this
con. Could speak would have
a solution what does that mean in
English. Suggest we take short walk.
Your office. I don't. Want to.
Be there right away. Well wait
a couple in stead of your short walk I
want to short ride to my office. Boys to
prepare make
a list. Of silent. I
didn't do it I tell you because I'm cold
you try to hang it on me and I for you to
pick lighter or I shall be faced with
quinine so you can pull up on me go to just
say arms. If you anything
to say the Rome has
nothing to do with it. Well.
About it. Save yourself
a lot of money for turning state's evidence
I have nothing to confess I have always
acted in good faith. That's
all from. My.
Waist to. Get out of
a pro last thing I do. Have no
idea and no one with proper.
Baby's fingers can move to. What
do you mean. The leave the head.
To secure my desired
confession. I don't see
why we shouldn't call it that it's morbid
nonsense it's no use complaining about it
. When you're here rather.
Modern. Charlie thank you.
Chris everyone takes aim
positions. But we've been.
Over that are. Surely outside
of discovered yes it.
Inconvenience of bringing everyone
here tonight mode to the recent. Like
tangle of men he's doing. So.
By persons in this through.
This thing held by his psychic medium.
Professor Bowen and cannot have
one hundred thousand dollars in damage
to lose by changing with. The same T.
. Deprive Mr Phelps administrators of
his state from handling logic far too.
As
a team. He had recently big
losses in stock market. Caretaker
. Own Time grudge against
Alan Kohler before
tragedy to talk with.
Others during. Family who
have everything to lose if Alan Kohler
return to claim the state. Tonight
will try various students to
experiment. To untangle motives.
We call. Upon fish. For Mr from great P.R.
. Proceed please to gauge
where you turned the lights.
For the moment.
I feel. Pretty.
Clear. It is
a woman. Trying
to come to us. Is becoming.
Clear. She is trying to be. She has
a message
a message for. You
. I.
Discovered.
Someone make a video course
misspeak. All night but it's been
a drip correction. May come our.
Well look at here here you have to die to
really find out how much people miss you
and why did you see it I like Charlie
straight. Sincerely hope makes the nation
justified cause of
anguish. Through all this
knife. Or so killer when
Colby would return to claim
a state. Body behind secret panel.
Then you are violent or
a device to make body appear
as aberration and. Same.
Also tried to kill him is no night business
conference but make mistake of shooting
dummy we tumble soap and Mr Martin
plays the do we. Not in this
room. Use twin of knives
but cute I could be.
Both and I think if I stood up right here
someone asked me about our hired someone
to. Be with you while Rick. Was already
over someone you went for that night I
didn't I tell you I think.
You are going to man I go crazy
contradiction. To precaution
before SALES Can I had to
cover a blade of a knife with
a graphite. Fingers signed
confession back everybody.
You commit murder in attempt to cover
evidence particularly in law or the count or
night tonight convict you.
Know you had nothing to do with this. Very
great food full value belief to believe
that tonight you practice deception this
time which I can say the same for you.
After all I'm the one who was imposed upon
and I would try all charges against them
market versus will think there's
a train Eastern eleven forty five. Back.
You take now. I think you are
right now we can stagger
down to
a comfortable basis. So sorry
but. Must return to happy
family. You've done a great job
Charlie. I wish I could make you
a present of the city all you. Can really
continue to increase it may consider
a generous offer but I don't
know thank you so much.